解决方案就是为DetailActivity类发送一个
The solution is to lauch an explicit intent to
显式声明的Intent。我们先转到onCreateView,
the Detail Activity Class. We'll go to On Create View,
这里我们定义了onItemClickListener方法。
where our On Item click listener is defined. To
我们可以使用Intent的Extra来传递天气预报的信息，
pass in the Weather Forecast information, we can use an
在Intent中它是以键值对的方式存储的。
intent extra, which is a key value pair in
这里我们使用key:Intent.EXTRA_TEXT，但其实我们
the Intent. We use the key name, Intent.extratext, but we
可以使用任何字符串。只要
can use any string for the key. As long as
我们读取信息时就会用到相同的key就好。
we use the same key when reading the information out.
总而言之，我们从
Just as in the toast, we obtain the forecast
当前的列表项获得预报数据，只要在所给的位置调用
data from the current list item, by calling get
adapter中的getItem方法即可。
item on the adapter at the given position. Once
当我们添加了Intent后，我们就能启动activity了。
we've added the intent, we just start the activity.